Allahu Akbar
La Elaha Ella Allah
Alhamdu Lillah. We praise God. Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
And we bear witness that there is no god except the one true God.
It all began a few billion years ago when an angel named Satan
entertained supercilious thoughts that he can be a god besides God.
And God decided that one way of letting Satan find out is to call his bluff
and make him a god. Now, a god cannot be a god without two things: a dominion and constituents and to
provide Satan with a dominion, God created a billion galaxies containing a billion trillion stars
contained in a universe that is 26 billion light years across.
And to emphasize the insignificance
the insignificance of Satan's dominion to be which is the planet Earth,
God created six other universes even bigger than this one.
And then eventually, God told Satan that this little mote in the smallest and innermost universe
called planet Earth will be your dominion. God equipped the planet Earth with the means
to support life for plants, animals and humans. No other place in the universe is so equipped.
And to provide Satan with constituents, God created a minute creature from
clay, a lowly material, named him Adam and then God ordered the angels to fall prostrate before
Adam. They all did except for the haughty one. He refused. Now, this is God's mercy.
Had God punished Satan for his supercilious thoughts without exposing them, the angels
would have been really perplexed. Why... What did God do this for? Satan didn't
do anything because the angels are not aware of Satan's innermost thoughts like God is.
So, God exposed Satan as a haughty rebel.
And then told him that he will have this dominion and these constituents
the descendants of this creature Adam who happen to agree with Satan's point of view
namely that God alone is not enough. We have two points of view: God's point of view that
God alone is the absolute Lord and Master, no one else and then we have the other point of
view that God alone is not enough that we can have some other lords and masters besides God.
So, all the human beings, the descendants of Adam, who agree with Satan's point of view
were destined to be Satan's constituents.
Satan's constituents were not assigned to him
involuntarily. God consulted each one of us. He asked us do you want to take a test where you
choose between My point of view and another point of view? Do you want to take a test where you choose
between Me as your only Lord and Master or to have another lord and master besides Me?
Every constituent of Satan was consulted. Every single human being was consulted.
And we said yes. The human being said yes. Other creatures said no. They were afraid.
We... there must have been incentives that made us agree to take the test.
One incentive is the fantastic, the awesome reward for those who make it, those who pass the test.
That is a positive incentive. The other reason probably was that we overestimated
our intelligence. We said of course, we're gonna choose You. You know, it's gonna be
stupid if we choose anybody else. We're gonna take the test. You and I said that.
So, Satan's constituents were assigned to him after they... they chose with their
free will to take the test and after they decided to side with Satan's point of view.
Now, once this was agreed on, the agreement stipulated that every
human being will be born into this world with instinctive God-given knowledge about God.
In addition to this, God will send messages
and messengers to continuously remind the human being to worship God alone.
The other side, Satan is given, is allowed to reproduce every time a human being is
born. Every time a baby is born, Satan is allowed to reproduce. Another baby of Satan is
also born, at the same time. And will attach... this piece of Satan will attach itself to
the human being from birth to death and will continuously talk Satan's point of view to you
and me to the human being saying God alone is not enough. You have to have Muhammad
or Jesus or Mary or this saint, also. They can help you, too. God alone is not enough.
And you with your instinctive knowledge and with the messages that you receive
are supposed to talk Satan's ambassador, representative who is your... he has your name.
You're supposed to talk Satan's representative into worshipping God Alone that Satan is wrong.
This companion is a descendent of Satan and he can go any way, either way, he or she. Same with you.
So, this is the agreement and this is the test that is happening, right now.
Immediately, Satan went to work on Adam
and Eve. They were living in Paradise during their innocence
and you and I and all of us, we were in Adam and Eve.
And Satan fooled us and made us break God's law.
When I wrote a script for a movie, I showed this Universal conference of all the human beings
who are destined to come on this planet Earth
bearing witness that God alone will be our Lord and Master and then, I showed all these souls, all of
the human beings combining together. Symbolically, I made it look like a DNA molecule. All the souls
combined together in a DNA molecule and then this one United soul was thrust into Adam's clay body.
So, we were all... this is my understanding, my comprehension of it, we were all in Adam
and we all broke God's law. This is why we are here and this is exactly how the plan was to work.
So, eventually Satan fooled Adam, tricked him, made him break God's law and then Adam, Eve, Satan and
and all those who agreed with Satan... there seems to be a number of other angels maybe
who also fell with Satan became jinns. The definition of a jinn is a fallen angel. Your
companion is a jinn, a descendant of Satan, the father of all the jinns, or the first jinn.
Adam, Eve, Satan and anyone who agreed with Satan's point or who broke God's law
or agreed with Satan's point of view were sent to prison. And their prison is this universe, our universe, 26 billion light
years across. This is Satan... Satan's prison cell and it's too small for him.
He can't go... he and his descendants cannot go beyond the smallest and innermost universe.
This is his prison cell.
And we read in the Quran that they continuously try to break, escape,
break out of it and go listen to the secrets in the other universes
and they can't because this is... this is a well-guarded universe, our universe.
Our universe again has a billion galaxies
and our neighbor galaxy next door is two million light years away. So, this shows you
the insignificance of Satan's dominion. The earth and everything on it, if it disappeared right now,
nothing will happen to God's domain. Nothing. You go to the edge of our galaxy, the Milky Way,
you will not even see the solar system let alone the planet Earth. You cannot see the
solar system which is four million miles across. You cannot see it from the edge of our universe.
Now, what I want to share with... this is an introduction only for the second KHUTBA
I want to share with you a personal experience that teaches all of us the limitations of Satan
and the whole idea of creating these seven universes and the whole human race.
Tooboo Ela Allah. Repent.
Alhamdu Lillah, we praise God. Wa Ash-hadu Alla Elaha Ella Allah Wahdahu La Shareeka Lah.
and we bear witness that there is only one God. We worship only one God. We side with God's point of view
that God Alone is our Lord and Master, that there is no other creature, no
saint, no prophet, nobody can help us or harm us, dead or alive. Only God is our Master and only God
hires and fires and gives health and happiness. Only God. What I want to share with you
is a conclusion
that is... that is very solid in my mind and the minds of most of you that Satan decided
since he is to whisper to us and talk us into accepting his point of view. This is the agreement.
That, he instead of wasting his time with the followers, he will capture the leaders.
the Pope. 900 million Catholics listen to the Pope. So, why should he waste his time with
900 million people when you can just capture one?
In Muslim countries religious schools
Al-Azhar in Egypt, for example
Children start going from... from first grade. Al-Azhar has from first grade to the Ph.D. level
and certain children will start Al-Azhar from the first grade and
Satan knows that these children will grow up to be religious scholars
who will lead the people and will teach them the religion.
The Imams that... I'm talking about the Imams of jurisprudence, Shafi'i, and Malek and Ibn Hanbal and those.
Millions of people follow them... followed them. So, why should he waste his time with
individuals when he can catch the leader and mislead the millions by misleading one leader?
So, this is his method. So, this... this has been his tactic ever since
he came down to this earth was to look for the leaders and catch them, possess them.
And it's very easy in the... in the Muslim countries, there is the Islamic University
in Medina and everybody's going there is going to teach other people.
So, he's always gonna take these people, he and his assistants or just him by himself.
He possess all those kids, all the students. So, they graduate into his lap
and they do his orders. They carry out his commands. Now, my personal experience
the miracle of the Quran
has grown to overwhelming proportions. It is going to overwhelm the world and I'm
going... let me interrupt here and give you the latest development. This was discovered
yesterday or the day before yesterday and it's very quick but it shows you how the miracle is
growing to undeniable proportions. It's going to overwhelm even the enemies of the Quran.
What was discovered yesterday or the day before yesterday was that the Quran contains numbers
1, 2, 3, 4, 5 up to 12 and then 19 and then 20, 30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 80, and then after 80
comes 99, and then 100, 200, 300, 1000, 2000, 3000, 5000, 50,000, 100,000.
These are all the numbers in the Quran without repetitions, of course, as you know. When
you add these numbers, the total is 162,134. I may be mistaken I think it is 16... 162,134
Maybe not, but after the KHUTBA, I can give you the correct number. The total is
fixed. It doesn't matter if I make mistakes or not. It is fixed. It is in the Quran. It is a multiple of
19. It is 19 times 8534. This is the latest discovery and let me add one more
minute of elaboration on why this is miraculous. For example, the number 50, there's only one number 50 in
the Quran. And it is written like this: Noah lived with his people 1,000 years less 50. So, it was not
written 950. Another place says We summoned Moses for 30 nights and increased them by 10. So, you can
see how the numbers stay independent and how they add up to a divisible total. If you do not make a
sacrifice under certain conditions during Hajj, sacrifice of an animal, you're supposed to fast
3 days during Hajj and 7 days when you go home which adds up to 10 where the Quran says
that. Of course, we know three and seven is 10, but that's essential to have the number 10. So, you
can... you can see how the mathematical composition of Quran and how miraculous it is beyond human
capability. So, this miracle is growing to overwhelming proportions and Satan knew about it.
And I assure you he did everything possible in his capacity to stop it from coming out
because now the cat is out of the bag like they say. He can do nothing now. It's too late.
I believe he even started a whole new religion based on the number 19 just to divert. Because
this did divert some people from the number 19, some Muslims, so-called Muslims. So, he did the impossible.
So, how did God hide it,
this miracle to surprise Satan? If Satan catches the people going to Al-Azhar
schools or the religious schools and possesses them, why can't he
possess the person who is working on the miracle of Quran? Now, here's what happened.
At the time... at the time, I started computers for the first time. I was working for Monsanto
Company. I was a senior research chemist at Monsanto Company and they decided to
computerize their chemical research. So, they gave us a crash course in computer six months.
And they told us to practice anything, do anything with the computer just to practice and this
happened to coincide, coincidence, with my desire to know what A.L.M. is and these
letters in the Quran. So, I said okay let me write the whole Quran in the computer and see if these
letters have any mathematical relations. So, I did... I wrote the whole Quran. I got all the results, all the counts, the
raw data. I have the raw data with me and there was an American Chemical Society meeting in Chicago
that was in August 1970, August 1970. I don't usually remember
the dates, but God made me remember some crucial dates because it's...
So, at this meeting, this man comes to me and he says we want you to work for us.
Who are you? I'm Robert Seely. I'm director of research for Anheuser-Busch. I said forget it.
I didn't say that. I said Sorry. Thanks but no thanks. He said we'll give you twice as much money. I said sorry. It's
not a matter of money. It's just in my religion, we're against alcohol and it'll be hypocritical of me to... to
work in the biggest brewery in the world when my religion prohibits it. And I happen to
be strongly religious. He said well, I assure you this has nothing to do with alcohol. I mean, rest
assured this will give you twice as much money and you'll have nothing to do with alcohol.
I said what is it? In fact, I said no thanks, still. You know, I just don't wanna be
connected with the name Anheuser-Busch, the biggest brewery in the world. It's in St. Louis. It's a fact.
So, he explained to me. He said this is in the food research department and it has nothing
absolutely nothing... it has to do with eggs, vitamins, carbohydrates, processed foods, has nothing to do
with alcohol at all. I said thanks but no thanks. He said you know, here's a report from the United Nations
that the people in your country, in Egypt, your home country... I was not even a citizen then...
are going to starve in about 10 years. Don't you want to save them? Well, he's trying this angle,
good old Bob Seely. Okay. I said so, exactly what is the nature of my job there? He said Okay. We throw away
this amount of waste, this amount of oats, this amount of barley, this and that and we
want to save it from waste, wanna transform it to food. They have baker's yeast and they have brewer's
yeast and I can choose to work with the either one. They throw tons of yeast. Yeast is rich in protein.
And this is my specialty as a biochemist. Anyway, to make a long story short,
I accepted the job at Anheuser-Busch. I took my raw data. I left Monsanto company, August 31st
1969. We have a witness here, Douglas. And I started with Anheuser-Busch on September 1st
1970.
Took all my raw data with me and for the next four years, the miracle of
the Quran was produced in the biggest brewery in the whole world and this
is how... what I'm trying to share with you is Satan's limitations.
And some of you may have been played... playing a game as children where you hide something
and go and find it. And the best place to hide it, if I'm the person to look for it, is in my
pocket, right? If you can slip it in my pocket, I can't find it. I will look around everywhere else
but this is... this is one of the things that many children used to do. They hide the object
in the pocket of the person who's looking for it. So, imagine Satan looking at the planet earth
and he sees Al-Azhar. Oh, these people are gonna grow up and lead millions to teach them
about Islam and the Quran and so on. Let me get them. And he will look and see Anheuser, the biggest
brewery in the world. Nah, this is mine. This is my pocket. Forget it. But inside that biggest
brewery was the miracle of Quran came out. What does this tell us? It tells us that Satan, it
has limitations where he cannot, it does not know everything that's happening on the planet Earth.
God knows
what the heart of an ant out there is doing.
Every, every atom in the universe... this is a quotation from the Quran... not a single atom is out
of God's vision or control. But you can see Satan unable to detect a significant event like this.
It was hidden from him. So, he couldn't put up any obstacles against me.
And this is what I wanted to share with you.
Aqem Al-Salat
Allahu Akbar